[{"answer": "The title speaks for itself.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "What does \"Finally Free\" mean?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, I learned that I wasn't as forth right as I always wanted to be and thought I could be.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "When you finished the book and you covered this extraordinary story, and we'll come to some of the details, what did you learn about Michael Vick?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "I think the lowest moment was when I, you know, I had to tell my son that I was going to prison and that I was going to be going for two years.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "What was the lowest moment for you, of the whole thing?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "He just broke down crying.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Well, the situation came about when his mom told me he had been getting teased by some of his friends at school, which is solely my fault, which is a situation that was out of my control.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "How did you -- how did you explain it?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Yes, because, you know, I always had a passion for animals and I always had a dog.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "What you saw as an 8-year-old boy, although horrific, seemed exciting to you, did it?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "And they'll say, how can you be a dog lover when you killed a lot of dogs because they were too weak to fight?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "I know it may seem contradictory but, you know, that's just the person that I was.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "How can you be a dog lover that enjoys doing that, too?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Nobody.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "No parent, no family, no friend?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "You know, I enjoyed the competition aspect of it.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "When you were doing it, did you enjoy it?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Just before the wall came crashing down on your life, you were the $130 million superstar.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "And for what?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes, it did.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Did it make you somebody that now you don't really recognize?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I was on the golf course.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What did you think the moment you heard this has happened?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I lied to my mom.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Did you lie to them?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "I told her the truth the day I got -- I got arraigned.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "What was the moment you told your mother the truth?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "She was just upset, disappointed.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "How did she react?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Harder.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "I mean those first few weeks?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "You know, I overlook it.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What do you say to those who say the crime you did was just so awful, you shouldn't be even allowed to play football anymore?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I understand it.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Do you blame them or do you understand it?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "You know, I was elated, you know, to get back home to my family, you know, more than anything.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "What was that moment like for you?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, before I even got home.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Did you vow to yourself, you know, I'm never going to put my kids in this sort of position again?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "What do you feel you owe her?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "That's false.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Is it true the security alone for your wedding costs 300,000 dollars?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "That's false.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "No, that's absurd.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "What were you doing?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "You know, I'm so appreciative of my fans.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "The fact that you're not just perceived as a footballer, you're a notorious celebrity?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I think it's more important to be understood.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Or is it more important to you to be understood better?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Have you got a dog?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Maybe so.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "You going to get one?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "I mean, I would let them pick it out.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "It was all kind of crazy.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Or was it honestly more fun being the ne'er-do-well?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Do you know, I'm very, very happy today.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "How the devil are you?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "You do.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "I look different in that clip, huh?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the -- what happened in the weekend was just an administrative finality.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "How do you feel now that you're officially a single man again?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, the limited amount of time I spend in reality I quite enjoy.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "How is your life in reality at the moment?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes, I remember that interview very distinctly, Piers.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Have you become, you know, a little less excited about the whole nature of fame and celebrity?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Is there something society should do to try and put a lid on this before we all go completely mad?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "There isn't one, I don't think.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "What's the point of it all?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Are you an American resident yet?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I love the American people, all of them, every single individual.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Is America refusing to accept you as one of its own then, Russell?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Pretty good, mostly.", "docId": "120717pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How is your temper at the moment?", "qSentId": 612}]